uniqlo.co.uk 2016-06-27

# Privacy Policy & Cookies - UNIQLO

Uniqlo is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors to its website. This privacy policy ("Policy") explains how we collect, store and use personal data about you when you browse uniqlo.com website (the "Site"), shop with us or otherwise provide your personal data to us. These terms will apply regardless of how the Site is accessed and will cover any technologies or devices (if applicable) by which we make the Site available to you. It provides you with details about the types of personal data that we collect from you, how we use your personal data and the rights you have to control our use of your personal data. 

By continuing to use the Site and/or using the products and services made available to you on the Site, you are agreeing to the terms of this Policy. 

We will never sell any information about you to anyone. We are part of a larger company and we may share information with our parent and affiliated companies. 

For the purposes of the UK Data Protection Act 1998 (the "Act"), UNIQLO EUROPE LTD ("We") are the data controllers (as defined in the Act) of the personal data (as defined in the Act) which we collect from you or which you provide to us through the "Site". We guarantee to comply with the standards, procedures and requirements laid down in the Act to ensure that your personal data is kept secure and processed fairly and lawfully. 

### What Information do we collect?

You should be aware that this site is being monitored and may capture information about your visit that will help us improve the quality of our service. We may collect this information even if you do not register with us. We collect and process the following data: 

  * "Personal Information" comprising:  

    * Your name, e-mail address, billing address, delivery address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information and a password
    * Information which you provide when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by us or when you report a problem with our Site;
    * a record of your correspondence if you contact us at **helpme@uniqlo.eu**
  * Information about where you are on the internet (e.g. the URL you came from, IP address and Top Level Domain), your browser type, the country and telephone area code where your computer is located, the pages of our website that were viewed during your visit, the advertisements you clicked on, and any search terms that you entered on our Site ("User Information"). This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns and does not identify any individual.

We may also collect the above personal data from third parties who have your consent to pass your details to us. If you are using a data capture form then add the following: 

We will send you information according to the preferences you submitted via our data capture form. If you would like to change these preferences at any point, please email us at helpme.uniqlo.eu alternatively you can also write to us at: 

Data Protection   
UNIQLO EUROPE LTD   
6th Floor   
1 Kingsway   
London   
WC2B 6AN 

  * We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Uniqlo.com or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Uniqlo.com on other Web sites.

**Mobile (if applicable)**

  * When you download or use apps provided by UNIQLO or its affiliates and, where applicable, have requested or consented to location services, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as search results, and other personalised content. Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services. 

### Cookies

A Cookie is a small file placed on you computer when you visit a website. We use 'cookies' to keep track of your current shopping session to personalise your experience and so that you may retrieve your shopping basket at any time. Cookies also enable us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage pattern;
  * Store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests;
  * Speed up your searches, and
  * recognise you when you return to our site.

We do not use cookies to collect or store personal information. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site. For the settings of cookies, please refer to Help function within your computer. Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at www.AboutCookies.org. Read more about the individual cookies. 

When you create a shopping account while ordering online you will be given the option to receive information from UNIQLO by post, e-mail or telephone, about products, promotions or special offers which we feel may be of interest to you. In the event that you do not wish to be contacted for such purposes, ensure that you tick the appropriate box as you go through the registration process. You may unsubscribe from our contact list at any time by replying to a promotional e-mail with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line. 

### Registration

You agree that:

  * The Personal Information which you provide when you register as a customer is true, accurate, current and complete in all respects.
  * You will notify us immediately of any changes to the Personal Information by contacting us by e-mail **helpme@uniqlo.eu**.
  * You agree not to impersonate any other person or entity or to use a false name or a name that you are not authorised to use.
  * You will keep your registration information secure and not disclose it to any third party.

**Marketing (if applicable)**

  * Please note that your information may be used to send you details of those products or services that we offer that we have identified as likely to be of interest to you. If you indicated any preferences when providing us with your data, we will use these to determine what information we provide you with.
  * If at any point you would like to opt-out of receiving communications from us, or would like to change the channels (such as email or post) that we use to contact you, please contact us at **helpme@uniqlo.eu**. Alternatively you may wish to write to us at: 

UNIQLO EUROPE   
1 Kingsway - 6th Floor   
London   
WC2B 6AN 

  * From time to time we would like to be able to pass your information to carefully selected third parties that offer products or services that we have identified as likely to be of interest to you.
  * We will only do this if you have opted-in to receive such communications, for example when you completed a data capture form or placed an order with us.
  * By entering into an agreement with us when you (select from the following as applicable): placed an order, entered a competition or prize draw run by us or on our behalf, or joined our membership, you have consented to this use of your data. 

### Your right to access Personal Information

You have a right to access the Personal Information that we hold on you. If you would like to see a copy of any information we have related to you, or you believe the information we hold on you is incorrect, please send a written request to the address shown below. If you are requesting a copy of information a £10 fee is payable.

**For Consumers**

In addition, if you wish to unsubscribe from e-mail marketing communications that we send you, you can do this by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any e-mail newsletter we have sent to you or, alternatively, by visiting our e-mail newsletter preference center. 

UNIQLO gives you periodic information so you can stay up to date on what we are offering. You can easily unsubscribe at any time you want by calling our customer service department at helpme@uniqlo.eu or by the following unsubscribe link, which is contained in the e-mail. It takes some time to put opt outs in effect so you may still receive emails from us for several weeks after your request is received. 

We also use your e-mail address to confirm your order and to confirm shipment of your order and to respond to any inquiries you make on-line. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

Our business is constantly changing and to that extent our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions will also change. We may, from time to time e-mail reminders of our policies and terms of business, unless you have instructed us not to. You should check our website frequently to view recent changes. If you choose to visit the Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. Any changes to the Terms will be posted on the Site and the date at the bottom of these Terms will be amended to reflect when these Terms were last revised. 

### How does UNIQLO use the information collected?

We will treat all your Personal Information as confidential (although we reserve the right to disclose this information in the circumstances set out below).   
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we do not share your information with any third parties other than for the limited, explicit reasons specified below; neither are we in the business of selling it to others. 

We share Personal Information with our parent company and affiliates that either are subject to this Privacy Policy or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice. 

The Personal Information are shared on a limited basis from time to time to send postal mail and e-mail, remove repetitive information from customer lists, analyse data, provide marketing assistance and provide customer service. 

We will only disclose data to: 

  * Other companies within our Group of companies
  * Business partners
  * Suppliers we engage to process data on our behalf
  * Government bodies and law enforcement agencies
  * Successors in title to our business

  * Given that the Internet is a global environment, using it to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis.
  * We share Personal Information and User Information with our parent company and affiliates. We share it on a limited basis with agents we use from time to time to send postal mail and e-mail, remove repetitive information from customer lists, analyse data, provide marketing assistance and provide customer service.
  * The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"), although the data will always be held securely and in line with the requirements of UK data protection. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.
  * We use your Personal Information to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and for the specific purpose for which it was volunteered. In addition, if you supply us with your postal address online, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information regarding a new collection, new products, new store locations, or upcoming promotional offers or events.
  * If you do not wish to receive any communications form UNIQLO or otherwise wish to remove your name and Personal Information from our list, please contact us at helpme@uniqlo.eu.

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions; or protect the rights, property, or safety of the Site, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. However, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personal information for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this policy. 

In the case that UNIQLO, or substantially all of its assets are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of a merger, sale, consolidation or liquidation, customer information may be one of the transferred assets. 

You agree that you do not object to us contacting you for any of the above purposes whether by telephone, e-mail or in writing and you confirm that you do not and will not consider any of the above as being a breach of any of your rights under the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003. 

By using this Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. We do not sell or rent to other third parties any personal information that you provide to us, except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Policy. 

### Links to third party websites

Certain links within the Site may be to other unrelated third party companies that offer you the option to share your personal information with them. We will not share your Personal Information with those third party companies. 

Links provided on the Site to third party websites are provided as a convenience to you and we do not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from ours. We do not endorse or make any representations about any third party sites that may be accessible through this site. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information. 

The data you choose to give to unrelated third parties is covered by their privacy policies. Some third party companies may choose to share their personal data with us; that sharing is governed by that third party's privacy policy. 

We cannot be responsible for personal data that third parties may collect, store and use through their websites. You should always read the privacy policy of each website you visit carefully. 

How secure is your information? We are committed to offering our customers a safe and secure environment. Our servers utilise SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology to help protect your personal information. By using an SSL-compatible browser such as Microsoft Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox, you can help ensure that your personal information is processed confidentially. 

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information, in our possession, may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you. If a notification is appropriate or required by law, we would endeavour to do so as promptly as possible, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. By using this Site, you consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification. 

Questions and enquiries related to this policy should be directed to:   
Data Protection   
UNIQLO EUROPE LTD.   
6th Floor   
1 Kingsway   
London   
WC2B 6AN 

© UNIQLO EUROPE LTD. 2014   
Registered in England & Wales - Number 4845064   
VAT Number - 820605757   
Last Updated – October 2015
